<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>DefLoadCache</name>
  <author>FluxxField</author>
  <packageId>fluxxfield.defloadcache</packageId>
  <modVersion>1.2.0</modVersion>
  <url>https://github.com/FluxxField/rimworld-defload-cache</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <description>Dramatically reduces RimWorld launch time on repeat loads by caching the results of mod XML loading and patch application.

On the first launch with a given mod list, DefLoadCache builds a cache of the fully-patched def tree. On subsequent launches with the same mod list, it skips reading thousands of XML files from disk and re-running thousands of XML patches, loading the cached result instead.

Tested on a 576-mod load order: launch time reduced from ~14 minutes to ~8 minutes (45% faster). The mod XML loading and patch application pipeline specifically goes from ~6 minutes to ~23 seconds.

Features:
- Automatic cache invalidation when mods, RimWorld version, or DLLs change
- Per-file fingerprinting catches any file change, even same-size content edits
- Profile-aware cache management, keeps one cache per saved mod list profile
- Binary XML cache format for fast deserialization on repeat launches
- Skips unnecessary patch validation on cached launches
- Configurable settings with per-feature toggles
- Zero gameplay impact: only affects load time

Safety:
- Pre-load cache validation verifies the cache file is intact before using it
- Post-load validation verifies per-mod def counts against baseline
- Self-healing: bad caches are automatically deleted and rebuilt
- Full fallback coverage: every entry point has error handling, the mod should never crash the game
- Memory-conscious: cache files stream directly to/from disk, no large memory allocations
- One-click "Test without cache" button for isolating issues
- Structured log output for modders reviewing player bug reports

Requires Prepatcher by Zetrith.</description>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>zetrith.prepatcher</packageId>
      <displayName>Prepatcher</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2934420800</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>zetrith.prepatcher</li>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
